Swetank Subham

+91 9110-09-0019

swetanksubham.r@gmail.com • https://swetanksubham.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/swetank-subham/

Software Engineer, with around **3 years** of experience in Software **Back-End Development** and **Management**, which includes several web apps and scripts. I describe myself as a life-long learner, implementer and **Data Science** enthusiast. I prefer smart work but always there for hard work if required.



Experience

09/2021 till Present

Software Developer

Knowlarity Communications Pvt. Ltd., Gurgaon

 Working on cloud-based communications technology and digital call center like IVR.

07/2019 to 09/2021

Software Engineer

Great Software Laboratory Pvt. Ltd., Pune

- Designed and developed several web apps.
- Developed and consumed date over Restful Web Services.
- Deployed web apps and worked on security headers configurations in production using Apache webserver.
- Perform ETL operation with pdf, excel, databases, csv.
- Worked with Apache Spark for Streaming ETL.
- Worked with Python Tesseract and OpenCV for OCR and image manipulation, respectively.
- Worked on database schema design and implementation.
- Worked with different python-based frameworks like Django,
 Pandas, OpenCV, Tesseract, Sanic, RASA, PySpark.
- Worked with OpenStack cloud technology for VM create and management.
- Worked with Docker technology for containerization of applications.

08/2018 to 06/2019

Software Engineer (Intern) Great Software Laboratory, Pune

- Worked on several web apps and developed one from scratch.
- Worked with MySQL database.

Skills

Python Shell Scripting JavaScript

Pandas Git Jira Linux Docker

Data Structures HTML CSS OOP

Tesseract Agile Methodology PHP

MySQL OpenCV PySpark RASA

Sanic Apache Spark JSON Pickle

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering

Lovely Professional University, Punjab

Certification

Data Structures and Algorithms

Nano Degree, Udacity

Data Science A-Z[™]

MOOCs, Udemy

Hobbies

- Playing Cricket
- Learning new technology